boredofstudies.org 2010-06-12

# Privacy Policy

I Study Australia Pty Limited, is committed to adopting the highest standards to safeguard our members personal information. I Study Australia, like other companies operating in Australia, is bound by the National Privacy Principles as set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000. I Study Australia's collection, use and disclosure of personal information is set out below:

## What Personal Information does I Study Australia collect and why?

I Study Australia collects personal information about you in order to provide personalised information services. The personal information you provide to I Study Australia will enhance the products and services that we offer you. The type of personal information we collect may include your name, address, telephone numbers, information on how you use our products and services (such as the type, date, time, or location, and personal preferences). 

## How I Study Australia may use your Personal Information 

The personal information you provide I Study Australia may be used for a number of purposes connected with our business operations, which include:

  * providing you with products and/or services requested;
  * billing you or administering your account;
  * dealing with requests, enquiries or complaints and other customer care related activities;
  * carrying out market and product analysis and marketing our products and services generally;
  * contacting you about our companies' products and services;
  * registering your details and allocating or offering you rewards, discounts or other benefits and fulfilling any requests or requirements you may have in respect of our and our group companies' loyalty or reward programmes and other similar schemes; and
  * carrying out any activity in connection with a legal, governmental or regulatory requirement on us or in connection with legal proceedings, crime or fraud prevention, detection or prosecution.

We may also use your personal information for purposes related to those described above which would be reasonably expected by you. To opt-out of receiving certain I Study Australia marketing materials, please email [unsubscribe@boredofstudies.org](mailto:unsubscribe@boredofstudies.org?subject=Unsubscribe). Please note that I Study Australia will still need to send you essential information about your account. We will not use your information for purposes other than described above unless we have your consent or there are specified law enforcement or public health and safety reasons. 

## Sharing your Personal Information

I Study Australia may disclose or receive personal information or documents about you to/from:

    * law enforcement agencies to assist in the prevention of criminal activities;
    * our service and content providers, dealers and agents, or any company within the I Study Australia group for purposes that are related to providing you with an information service which would be reasonably expected.

Unless you consent, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties, other than those who have contracted with I Study Australia to keep the information confidential, or who are subject to obligations to protect your personal information.

## Security of your Personal Information

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment protected from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. How to access your personal information upon your request, I Study Australia will take reasonable steps to let you know, generally, what sort of personal information we hold, for what purposes and how we collect, use and disclose that information. Upon your request, I Study Australia will provide access to your personal information we hold, except in certain prescribed circumstances, including emergency situations, specified business imperatives and law enforcement or other public interests. 

## How to contact us

If you have any queries or concerns, please contact us by phoning **(02) 8006 1886**.
